HEY.
Both:
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING UP?
OH, WE WANTED TO FINISH
THE CROSSWORD
BEFORE WE
WENT TO BED.
DO YOU KNOW
A SIX-LETTER WORD FOR RED?
DARK RED.
YEAH, I THINK
THAT'S WRONG
BUT THERE'S A CONNECT-THE-DOTS
IN HERE FOR YOU LATER.
HEY, HOW ABOUT MAROON?
YES. YOU ARE SO SMART.
AH.
YOU GUYS ARE SO CUTE.
I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL SEE YOU
IN THE MORNING.
OKAY.
I LOVE DOING CROSSWORD
PUZZLES WITH YOU, HONEY.
AH. ME, TOO.
LET'S FINISH THIS
AND GO TO BED.
OKAY.
THERE'S ONLY ONE LEFT.
THREE-LETTER WORD...
NOT DOG, BUT..
CAT.
YES!
YOU ARE SO SMART.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
UH...
WE STILL
NEED A TIP.
ALL RIGHT.
HOLD ON.
I GOT IT.
NICKEL.
HOW MUCH MORE DO WE NEED?
COUPLE OF BUCKS.
OKAY, DIME.
YOU GUYS SHOULD PROBABLY
KEEP TALKING.
THIS COULD TAKE AWHILE.
OH, NO, WAIT!
LOOKIT!
WHOA!
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS A POLICE BADGE.
WHY WOULD A COP
COME IN HERE, THOUGH?
THEY DON'T SERVE DOUGHNUTS.
COULD YOU DISCOVER
THE BADGE AGAIN?
I THINK I CAN COME
UP WITH SOMETHING
BETTER THAN THAT.
I BET SOMEBODY'S
MISSING THAT BADGE.
YEAH, I SHOULD PROBABLY
TAKE IT BACK.
OOH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHILE I'M AT THE POLICE STATION
I COULD CHECK THEIR
TEN MOST WANTED LIST.
'CAUSE MY FRIEND FRITZY'S BEEN
NUMBER 11 FOR, LIKE, EVER
SO THIS COULD BE HER YEAR.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HEY, JOEY.
HEY.
HI.
IS THAT, UH...
IS THAT MY SWEATSHIRT?
OH, YES, IT IS.
I'M SORRY. I BORROWED IT.
I WAS COLD.
I-I HOPE IT'S OKAY.
UH, WELL, IT'S JUST THAT, UH...
YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE
WEARING SOMEONE'S SWEATSHIRT
SHOULDN'T IT BE
YOUR BOYFRIEND'S?
YOU KNOW... AND I'M NOT HIM.
I'M SORRY. I'LL GIVE IT
BACK TO YOU.
NO, NO.
NO. IT'S GOING TO BE
ALL SMELLING LIKE MONICA.
ARE YOU SAYING I SMELL BAD?
NO. NO, YOU SMELL LIKE
A MEADOW.
I'M SORRY. I...
WHAT'S WITH HIM?
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE LAST TIME THAT JOEY WENT
TO A MEADOW
HIS MOTHER WAS SHOT BY A HUNTER.
OH!
YEAH, I STILL DON'T KNOW.
I'M SORRY, I JUST WANT TO MAKE
SURE I BOUGHT THE RIGHT COUCH.
I NEED A COUCH THAT SAYS
"KIDS WELCOME HERE"
BUT THAT ALSO SAYS...
"COME HERE TO ME."
WHAT?
YOU SAY THAT TO KIDS?
NO, NO, NO.
THE "COME HERE TO ME" IS...
YOU KNOW, FOR THE LADIES.
ROSS, HONEY,
IT'S A NICE COUCH.
IT'S NOT A MAGIC COUCH.
YOU PICKED
A GREAT COUCH.
YEAH?
COULD YOU SIGN
HERE, PLEASE?
WHOA, WHOA. WHAT'S...?
THE DELIVERY CHARGE IS ALMOST
AS MUCH AS THE COUCH.
WAIT, NO. THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
COME ON, HE LIVES
THREE BLOCKS AWAY.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL TAKE IT
MYSELF, THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT, RACH, COME ON.
LET'S GO.
YEAH.
( laughing )
ARE YOU KIDDING?
NO, COME ON.
IT'S ONLY THREE BLOCKS.
IT'S NOT VERY HEAVY.
TRY IT. COME ON.
( frustrated grunt )
OH! OH, I CAN DO IT.
YEAH.
YOU TWO WILL REALLY
ENJOY THAT COUCH.
OH, YEAH,
WE'RE, UH...
YEAH, WE'RE
NOT TOGETHER.
OH. OKAY.
( laughing )
SOMETHING DIDN'T
QUITE ADD UP THERE.
ROSS...
WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
ROSS...
YOU... HER...
I MEAN, SHE'S VERY...
YOU KNOW...
AND YOU'RE LIKE...
NOT THAT IT'S ANY OF YOUR
BUSINESS, BUT WE DID GO OUT.
REALLY? YOU TWO?
YEAH. RACH?
I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO BE DOING THIS RIGHT NOW.
I'M CARRYING A VERY HEAVY COUCH.
THEN TELL HIM QUICKLY.
FINE. WE WENT OUT.
NOT ONLY DID WE GO OUT
WE DID IT... 298 TIMES.
ROSS!
OH, MY...
OH! YOU KEPT COUNT?!
YOU ARE SUCH A LOSER.
A LOSER YOU DID IT WITH
298 TIMES.
OH! OH!
MA'AM! EXCUSE ME, MA'AM?
YES?
YOU CAN'T PUT YOUR
CIGARETTE OUT ON A TREE.
YEAH, I CAN.
IT WORKED REAL WELL.
NO, BUT YOU SHOULDN'T.
SO DON'T EVER DO THAT AGAIN.
I WON'T...
TILL I HAVE MY NEXT CIGARETTE.
HOLD IT.
N.Y.P.D.
FREEZE, PUNK.
WHAT?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU ARE SO BUSTED.
( laughing )
UH, BOOK 'EM.
WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
SAVE IT, RED!
UNLESS YOU WANT TO SPEND
THE NIGHT IN THE SLAMMER
YOU APOLOGIZE TO THE TREE.
I AM NOT GOING TO
APOLOGIZE TO A TREE.
YOU APOLOGIZE TO
THE TREE RIGHT NOW
OR I AM CALLING FOR BACKUP.
BACKUP! BACKUP!
I-I'M SORRY! SORRY!
OKAY, CANCEL BACKUP!
CANCEL BACKUP!
OKAY.
ROSS, DIDN'T YOU SAY
THAT THERE WAS AN
ELEVATOR IN HERE?
UH, YES, I DID, BUT THERE ISN'T.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
OKAY, GO LEFT. LEFT.
OKAY.
LEFT!
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S NO MORE LEFT LEFT.
OH, OKAY.
YOU KNOW, LIFT IT STRAIGHT UP
OVER YOUR HEAD.
STRAIGHT UP OVER YOUR HEAD.
YOU CAN DO IT.
( grunting )
OKAY. YOU GOT IT?
YEAH. GO. GO.
OKAY, YOU GOT IT, RIGHT?
YOU GOT IT, RIGHT?
RIGHT. YEAH.
( screams )
ANY CHANCE YOU THINK THE
COUCH LOOKS GOOD THERE?
SO, THIS GUY WAS ALL
( mumbles )
AND I'M ALL,
"BUFFAY. HOMICIDE."
IT WAS JUST SO COOL.
PHOEBE, YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO TAKE
THAT BACK.
I KNOW, BUT I'M HAVING
SO MUCH FUN DOING GOOD DEEDS.
OKAY, BUT IMPERSONATING A POLICE
OFFICER'S A SERIOUS THING.
YOU COULD GET ARRESTED.
YOU COULD GET ARRESTED
RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT, YEAH,
I BETTER TAKE IT BACK.
TOTALLY DRUNK WITH POWER.
HEY.
OH, I...
HI, JOE.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU GUYS
WERE GOING TO BE HERE.
HEY, JOEY?
DO ME A FAVOR, SWEETIE.
TASTE THIS.
WHAT? WHY?
WHAT IS GOING ON
WITH YOU?
NOTHING.
YOU'VE BEEN ACTING STRANGE
ALL DAY.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE IS SOMETHING.
I, UH...
I KIND OF HAD A DREAM...
BUT I DON'T WANT TO TALK
ABOUT IT.
WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
WHAT IF MARTIN LUTHER KING
HAD SAID THAT?
I... KIND OF HAVE A DREAM.
I DON'T WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
IT INVOLVED MONICA.
YOU HAD A DREAM ABOUT
A GIRL THAT I'M SEEING?
OH, THAT IS SO COOL.
SO MANY TIMES I DREAMT
ABOUT A GIRL THAT
HE WAS SEEING.
ANYWAY, WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT YOUR DREAM.
I LOVE YOU. YOUR DREAM?
THERE WASN'T ANY SEX IN IT
OR ANYTHING.
I HAVEN'T DREAMT ABOUT HER
LIKE THAT
SINCE I FOUND OUT ABOUT
YOU TWO... ISH.
WHAT WAS THE DREAM ABOUT?
WELL... OKAY.
YOU WERE MY GIRLFRIEND
AND WE WERE DOING
THE CROSSWORD PUZZLE--
YOU KNOW, LIKE YOU GUYS
WERE DOING LAST NIGHT.
SO, THAT'S IT.
I'M IN LOVE WITH MONICA
AND I'LL BE MOVING OUT.
WAIT, JOEY, JOEY.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT-THAT
YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH ME.
IT... IT DOESN'T?
NO, IT CAN
MEAN ANYTHING...
LIKE ALL OF A SUDDEN
YOU'RE JEALOUS
THAT I'VE BECOME
THE APARTMENT STUD.
KIND OF SOUNDS LIKE
YOUR DREAM, DUDE.
OR IT COULD MEAN THAT YOU SAW
CHANDLER AND ME TOGETHER
AND WE WERE BEING
CLOSE AND STUFF
AND-AND YOU JUST WANT
TO HAVE THAT WITH SOMEONE, TOO.
WELL, IN THE DREAM,
I DID ENJOY THE CLOSENESS.
Monica:
MM-HMM.
OKAY, LOOK, LOOK.
ARE YOU ATTRACTED TO MONICA?
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW,
ARE YOU ATTRACTED TO HER?
NOT REALLY.
WELL, THERE YOU HAVE IT.
WELL, SURE, I'M JUST
WEARING SWEATS.
BUT THAT'S GOOD...
THAT YOU'RE NOT
IN LOVE WITH ME
BECAUSE YOU JUST
WANT A GIRLFRIEND.
NO, I DON'T THINK
IT'S JUST ABOUT
JUST GETTING A GIRLFRIEND,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, YEAH, I COULD
GET A GIRLFRIEND.
YEAH, WE COULD SIT IN THE CHAIR
AND DO CROSSWORD PUZZLES
BUT WILL WE EVER HAVE THE
CLOSENESS LIKE YOU GUYS HAVE?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
MONICA AND I WERE FRIENDS
BEFORE WE STARTED DATING
SO MAYBE THAT'S IT.
FRIENDS FIRST?
THAT'S INTERESTING.
( chuckles )
YOU BECOME FRIENDS AFTER?
NO. NEVER DONE THAT, EITHER.
HEY... UM, DO YOU GUYS
HAVE A TAPE MEASURE?
OH, YEAH, IT'S ACTUALLY
IN MY BEDROOM.
( giggling )
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHAT'S UP, JOEY?
HOW YOU DOIN'?
OH... EXCUSE ME.
IS THIS YOUR CAR?
YEAH.
I DON'T THINK IT'S
VERY NICE OF YOU TO PARK HERE.
YOU'RE BLOCKING THE ENTRANCE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
WELL, IT'S A PROBLEM FOR ME
WHICH MEANS
IT'S A PROBLEM FOR YOU
'CAUSE I'M A COP.
SO AM I.
OH, NO.
OH, OKAY, SO YOU'RE A COP
WHICH MEANS
YOU CAN PARK ANYWHERE.
I KNOW THAT,
'CAUSE I'M A COP, TOO.
SORRY. KEEP UP THE GOOD WORK.
TEN-FOUR.
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
SO WHAT PRECINCT
ARE YOU WITH?
I-I'M WITH THE, UM, THE 57th.
OH, I KNOW A GUY IN
HOMICIDE UP THERE.
I'M IN VICE.
YEAH, IN FACT, I'M
UNDERCOVER RIGHT NOW.
I'M A WHORE.
WHO ELSE IS IN
VICE UP THERE?
UM, DO YOU KNOW,
UM, SIPOWITZ?
SIPOWITZ? NO,
I DON'T THINK SO.
YEAH, SIPOWITZ, YEAH.
BIG GUY, KIND OF BALD.
NAH, I DON'T KNOW HIM.
OKAY.
DON'T TRY
TO CALL HIM OR ANYTHING
'CAUSE HE'S NOT THERE.
HE'S OUT.
HIS, UM...
HIS PARTNER JUST DIED.
WOW. WELL, TELL SIPOWITZ
I'M REAL SORRY FOR HIS LOSS.
I-I SURE WILL.
TAKE CARE.
OKAY.
HEY, BY THE WAY
I'M SURE SIPOWITZ IS
GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
I HEARD THAT KID
FROM SILVER SPOONS
IS REALLY GOOD.
AND WHERE'D YOU
FIND MY BADGE?
OH.
HEY, JOEY,
WOULD YOU MIND
GIVING ME AND ROSS
A HAND MOVING HIS COUCH?
OH, I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I GOT ACTING CLASS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GUESS I COULD BLOW THAT OFF...
FOR YOU.
THANKS.
UH, SAY, RACHEL, LET
ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
UH, I WAS JUST OVER THERE
TALKING TO MONICA
AND CHANDLER
AND, BOY, THEY
ARE REALLY TIGHT.
I KNOW.
THAT'S NOT A BAD SITUATION
THEY GOT GOING OVER THERE.
UH-UH.
THINKING OF GETTING ME
ONE OF THOSE.
WHAT'S UP, JOE?
WELL, THE REASON I THINK
MONICA AND CHANDLER
ARE SO GREAT IS BECAUSE THEY
WERE FRIENDS FIRST, YOU KNOW?
SO I ASKED MYSELF,
WHO ARE MY FRIENDS?
YOU AND PHOEBE.
I SAW YOU FIRST, SO...
( nervous laughing )
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I'M SAYING, MAYBE YOU AND I
CRANK IT UP A NOTCH.
YOU KNOW, HONEY, UM, AS, UH...
AS FLATTERED AS I AM
THAT YOU SAW ME FIRST,
UH, I JUST...
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD BE
CRANKING ANYTHING UP.
WELL, I'LL TREAT
YOU REAL NICE.
OH-HO.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU KNOW, UM...
NO, HONEY, LISTEN, I THINK
IT'S A GREAT IDEA TO BECOME
FRIENDS WITH SOMEONE
BEFORE YOU DATE THEM
BUT THE WAY YOU DO IT IS,
YOU KNOW, YOU MEET SOMEONE
BECOME THEIR FRIEND,
BUILD A FOUNDATION
THEN ASK THEM
OUT ON A DATE.
DON'T HIT ON
YOUR EXISTING FRIENDS.
WELL, WON'T THAT
TAKE LONGER?
YEAH. YEAH.
OH, BUT ONCE YOU FIND IT,
OH, IT'S SO WORTH THE WAIT.
YEAH.
WELL, I UNDERSTAND.
I UNDERSTAND,
YOU KNOW.
MAN, I WISH I
SAW PHOEBE FIRST.
COME HERE TO ME.
NO, NO. YOU COME HERE TO ME.
HEY, ROSS.
( clearing throat )
I BROUGHT REINFORCEMENTS.
OH, GREAT. WHAT,
YOU BROUGHT JOEY?
WELL, I BROUGHT
THE NEXT BEST THING.
HEY.
CHANDLER? YOU
BROUGHT CHANDLER?
THE NEXT BEST THING
WOULD BE MONICA.
YOU KNOW,
I WOULD BE OFFENDED
BUT MONICA IS
FREAKISHLY STRONG, SO...
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
I-I DREW A SKETCH
OF HOW WE'RE GOING
TO DO IT, OKAY?
RACH, THAT'S YOU.
THAT'S THE COUCH.
MM-HMM. OOH, WHAT'S THAT?
OH, THAT'S ME.
WOW.
YOU CERTAINLY THINK
A LOT OF YOURSELF.
NO, THAT'S...
THAT'S MY ARM.
OH, I SEE.
I THOUGHT YOU JUST REALLY,
REALLY LIKED YOUR NEW COUCH.
YOU KNOW, JUST...
JUST FOLLOW MY LEAD.
OKAY.
COME ON,
CHANDLER.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT,
READY, SET, TURN.
OKAY.
TURN.
( screaming )
I DON'T THINK WE
CAN TURN ANYMORE.
ROSS, I JUST
DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO FIT.
OH, YEAH, IT WILL.
COME ON, UP.
UP, UP, UP.
UP!
HERE WE GO, PIVOT.
PIVOT!
PIVOT.
SHUT UP! SHUT UP! SHUT UP.
OKAY, I... I DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO PIVOT ANYMORE.
YOU THINK?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S, UH...
LET'S BRING IT BACK DOWN
AND TRY AGAIN.
OKAY. OH...
( grunting and groaning )
OKAY, YEAH. I THINK
IT'S REALLY STUCK NOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT DIDN'T WORK.
I KNOW. ME NEITHER.
I MEAN, YOU HAD A SKETCH.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU MEAN
WHEN YOU SAID PIVOT?
HEY.
HOW'S IT GOING?
DID YOU MAKE
ANY NEW FRIENDS?
YEAH. YEAH, I MET THIS WOMAN.
OKAY, WHOA, WHOA.
WHAT'S SHE LIKE?
UH, WELL...
SHE'S REALLY GOOD IN BED.
JOEY, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GOING TO TRY
TO BE FRIENDS FIRST.
WELL, HEY, IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
WHAT? WHY?
BECAUSE YOU
DIDN'T GIVE ME ADVICE.
NO, YOU GAVE ME
A PICKUP LINE.
AS SOON AS I TOLD HER
I WANTED TO BUILD A FOUNDATION
AND BE FRIENDS FIRST
I SUDDENLY--
THROUGH NO FAULT OF MY OWN--
BECAME IRRESISTIBLE TO HER.
AND HER ROOMMATE.
WHAT ABOUT
THE CLOSENESS?
CLOSENESS, SCHMOSENESS.
THERE WAS THREE OF US,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
ALL RIGHT, HEY, WHO WANTS PIZZA?
I DO. I DO. I DO.
OH, THIS
IS GREAT.
CAN YOU BELIEVE I FOUND THIS
ON THE SECOND FLOOR?
( knocking on door )
WHO IS IT?
Man:
N.Y.P.D.
OH, MY GOD.
UH... JUST A MINUTE,
OFFICER!
I'M LOOKING
FOR PHOEBE BUFFAY.
OH, MY GOD, IT'S HIM.
IT'S THAT COP.
GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HE FOUND ME.
MY GOD, PHOEBE.
ARE YOU GOING
TO GO TO JAIL?
WELL, IF I'M GOING DOWN,
YOU GUYS ARE GOING DOWN WITH ME.
WHAT?
HARBORING A FUGITIVE?
THAT'S
ONE-TO-THREE YEARS MINIMUM.
GOOD LUCK, CHANDLER.
OKAY, YOU CAN ARREST
ME, FINE, BUT YOU'LL
NEVER MAKE IT STICK,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
YEAH, BUT I
KIND OF DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
IT'S MY JOB. I MEAN,
YOU UNDERSTAND, RIGHT?
YEAH, AS LONG AS YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT I'M GOING TO CALL MY LAWYER
AND ONCE HE PUTS YOU
ON THE STAND
HE'S GOING TO MAKE YOU LOOK
LIKE A FOOL, LIKE A FOOL.
MM-HMM. I DON'T LIKE
LOOKING FOOLISH.
YOU KNOW WHAT? MAYBE, UH,
I DON'T ARREST YOU TODAY.
MAYBE I CAME BY
AND YOU WEREN'T HERE.
I WOULD LOVE IT
IF I WEREN'T HERE.
OKAY, SINCE, UM, YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO JAIL TONIGHT
I WAS WONDERING IF
YOU WOULD LIKE
TO GO TO DINNER WITH ME.
ME?
YEAH.
EVER SINCE YOU FLASHED
MY BADGE AT ME
I KIND OF CAN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE THE PRETTIEST FAKE
UNDERCOVER WHORE I'VE EVER SEEN.
NICE.
WOW, I DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING.
YOU'RE ASKING ME OUT.
YEAH, AND I COULD
HAVE DONE IT BETTER
BUT THESE PEOPLE
KEEP STARING AT ME.
UM... YEAH.
I-I'D LIKE TO GO OUT
WITH YOU, OFFICER.
GARY.
OKAY, SO IT'S A DATE?
YEAH. I GOT TO ASK.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHERE TO FIND ME?
YOUR FINGERPRINTS
WERE ALL OVER MY BADGE
SO I RAN THEM
THROUGH THE COMPUTER
AND THIS IS LISTED
AS YOUR LAST KNOWN ADDRESS
SO I CHECKED IT OUT.
OH, IMPRESSIVE.
NOT AS IMPRESSIVE AS YOU.
I LOOKED AT YOUR RECORD
AND YOU'VE DONE
SOME PRETTY WEIRD STUFF.
YEAH, WE'LL TALK AT DINNER.
OKAY. SO I'LL COME BY
IN A COUPLE HOURS
AND PICK YOU UP?
ALL RIGHT.
I CAN'T WAIT.
I'M NOT GOING TO JUST
TAKE YOU OUT FOR DOUGHNUTS.
( laughing )
HE HAS A GUN.
I'D LIKE TO RETURN THIS COUCH.
I'M NOT SATISFIED WITH IT.
YOU WANT TO RETURN
THIS COUCH?
IT'S CUT IN HALF.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TELLING YOU.
DID YOU CUT THIS
COUCH IN HALF?
THIS COUCH IS CUT IN HALF.
I WOULD LIKE TO EXCHANGE IT
FOR ONE THAT IS NOT CUT IN HALF.
YOU'RE TELLING
ME THIS COUCH
WAS DELIVERED
TO YOU LIKE THIS?
LOOK, I'M A REASONABLE MAN.
I WILL ACCEPT STORE CREDIT.
I'LL GIVE YOU
STORE CREDIT
IN THE AMOUNT
OF FOUR DOLLARS.
I WILL TAKE IT.